calcchat.com 2019-07-21

# CalcChat | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”), effective 02/13/2017, tells you about Larson Texts’ privacy practices governing personal information and permissions when you use the CalcChat website [www.CalcChat.com](http://www.calcchat.com/) (“Website”) and the CalcChat mobile apps for iOS and Android (“App”).

From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Policy. If our information practices do change materially, we will post the changes to our website and revise our Policy accordingly.

CalcChat is used to provide users with worked-out video solutions for problems found in Larson Texts textbooks. You can download the CalcChat app from the Apple Store or the Google Play Store. The CalcChat app requests permission to access your mobile device’s camera in order to use the QR Code reader feature. CalcChat also requests permission to access your mobile device’s storage so you can save your favorite videos.

CalcChat does not require you to enter personal information, such as email address or other personal identifiers, to use the Website or the App.

## Automatically Collected Information

The App may collect certain information automatically, including but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the App.

## Analytics

To determine how many users visit our site, how often they visit this site, and to better understand the areas of greatest interest to our visitors, we use a tools called “Google Analytics” to compile this information for us. As a result of your visit to our site, Google may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of analytics tools with personally identifiable information. For more information about the analytics companies’ ability to use and share information about your visits to this site, see <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to the Website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

## Third-Party Advertisers

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers use technology sent directly to your browser from the advertisements and links that appear on CalcChat. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

CalcChat has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. CalcChat’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, and to guard that information against loss, misuse, or alteration.

Please note, however, that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we use commercially-reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Links to Third Party Sites

This Policy applies only to information collected by this website. From time to time, this website may link you to other sites (“Linked Sites”) that are not owned by us. We do not control the collection or use of any information, including Personal Information, that occurs during your visit to the Linked Sites. Further, we make no representations about the privacy policies or practices of the Linked Sites, and we are not responsible for their privacy practices.

Be careful of disclosing any of your personally identifiable information when leaving our site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information.

## Questions About Our Privacy Policy and Practices

If you have any questions about the Policy or our privacy practices, you may contact:

Larson Texts  
1762 Norcross Road  
Erie, PA 16510
